macrium.com 2017-11-19

# Macrium Software | Terms & Privacy Policy

#### Terms

All purchases of Macrium Reflect software are subject to a 30-day, no question, money-back guarantee. In the unlikely event that you are not satisfied with your purchase, please [contact us](http://www.macrium.com/support.aspx#tickets) and your request will be dealt with promptly by our team.

All purchases made online via our website are fulfilled by our distribution partner cleverbridge Ag. Full details of their terms and condition and privacy policy are accessible via the links on the shopping cart page. Please note that Paramount Software UK Limited never have access to or store any of your credit card information.

#### Our Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Paramount Software UK Limited uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website or purchase our software via an approved reseller or distributor.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

#### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Name and job title
  * Contact information including email address, address and business name information if relevant
  * Other information relevant to licensing, customer support, surveys and/or offers

#### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping, including support and licensing information.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional email about available updates, our own products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone or mail.
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
  * We may provide your information to our approved reseller partners or distributor partners to enable them to complete any necessary transactions or function related to your purchase.
  * We will never sell your information to any third party.

#### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

#### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

#### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Any marketing email you receive from us will always include a link to easily unsubscribe from our marketing list.
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or   
[sending us a ticket](http://www.macrium.com/support.aspx#tickets).

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Paramount Software UK Limited, Kilburn House, Manchester Science Park, Manchester M15 6SE United Kingdom

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
